foodytv.com 2019-02-14

# 

    We know that by choosing to visit FoodyTV’s network, you've placed a great deal of trust in us. We also understand that
    you want the personal information you give us to be kept private as well as secure. To reassure you that we feel the same
    way, here's how we will and, more importantly, will not use the personal information you give us. If you have any questions
    please e-mail our Customer Happiness Team at i​ nfo@foodytv.com​ or call us at 1-866-415-0137.
1. What Information We Gather
   Traffic Data Collected
   We automatically track and collect the following information when you visit our Site: (i) your IP address; (ii) the type of
   computer you are using; and (iii) the type of Web browser you are using (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is helpful –
   in the aggregate -- for marketing purposes and for improving our customers’ over all experience of the Web site.
   Personal Information Collected
   We receive and store any information you enter anywhere on the Company's Site. For example, we may ask you to
   complete a registration form that asks for contact information (such as name, address, telephone number, and e-mail
   address). Additionally, If you communicate with us by e-mail, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest
   entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. You may choose not
   to provide us with certain Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and view much of the Site; however,
   you may not be able to view all content. In addition, you can choose not to provide certain optional information, but then
   you might not be able to take full advantage of many of the features on ​www.Foodytv.com​.
2. How We Use the Information We Gather
We use your Personal Information for such purposes as responding to your requests, processing and filling inquiries, verifying
your qualifications for certain products and services, billing, improving our services, providing an enhanced and more
personalized experience, communicating with you, and informing you of special offers and discounts. We may provide your
Personal Information to third parties to the extent necessary to fill your order or complete your inquiry. We may also share
your Personal Information as described in section 5 below. Except as provided above, and in section 5 below, we will not
release your Personal Information to a third party unless you have granted us permission to do so.
3. How We Use "Cookies"
A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. ​Foodytv.com​ uses cookies to
identify you as a previous visitor and to allow our systems to remember you as you browse our site. By allowing our systems
to set a cookie on your computer, you will not have to log in a password more than once per visit, thereby saving you time
while on our Site. Cookies can also enable us to learn your interests and enhance your experience on our Site. For example,
we use cookies to let us know that you are a prior viewer and to allow our systems to recall information on page selections
while on our Site. We do not store any Personal Information (except your e-mail address) or financial information about you
using cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of
cookies. If you disable this feature, you may still use our Site, but certain aspects with ​Foodytv.com​ may be impacted or
disabled.
4. Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic
information for anonymous and aggregate use.
5. Sharing of Personal Information
In addition to Section 2 above, we share demographic information with our partners and advertisers on an anonymous and
aggregate basis. This type of data is not readily linked to any personally identifiable information.
We work closely with third parties to bring you our services. We share information when another company is involved in the
transaction so that company can perform its functions.
6. Requesting Information from Potential and Registered Customers

Our Site provides (in areas accessible to nonregistered users) an order form for potential customers to request information
about our products and services. We may direct additional communications, including e-mail, to registered customers and
these potential customers that we deem may be of interest to them. Additionally, at times, we may request customer
feedback about our products, our services, or your past experiences, which may be displayed on our Site and in other
marketing materials. Participation in these programs is optional, and by participating you grant us a nonexclusive,
royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate, distribute, and
display all or parts of your feedback and you grant us permission to use your full name or your first name, last initial, and
neighborhood, as determined by ​Foodytv.com​, in connection with your feedback. To be removed from future ​Foodytv.com
e-mail campaigns ("opt out" request) you can simply access and update your information at the bottom of any email message
or notify us at ​info@foodytv.com​.
7. Market Research
Foodytv.com​ may secure the services of a market research firm to collect information from you to improve our service and
product mix. Your feedback is optional and results will be used in aggregate reviews.
8. Limits to Your Privacy
Our Site may contain links to other Web sites. ​Foodytv.com​ wants you to be aware that when you click on links and/or ad
banners that take you to third-party Web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies, not ours. While we
support the protection of privacy on the Internet, we are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties
and other Web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever
interacting with, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other Web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to
information collected by the Company on this Site.
9. Your Security
Foodytv.com​ takes precautions to protect your Personal Information. When our registration/order form asks users to enter
sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with encryption software.
Our Site encrypts your credit card number prior to transmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption
technology. This technology works best when the Site is viewed using a ​modern browser​ like Chrome, Safari or Firefox.
While we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your Personal Information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the
Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure or warrant the
security of any information you transmit to us or information we transmit to you from our online products or services, and you
do so at your own risk.
10. Your Consent and Changes to This Policy
By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of information by us in accordance with the terms of this Privacy
Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Site so you are always aware of what
information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. By continuing to use this site after
notice is given, you will have consented to our use of your information in this different manner. If at any time you would like
notice of changes to the Privacy Policy or the Customer Agreement, e-mail us at i​ nfo@foodytv.com​ ​from the e-mail address to
which you would like the notice sent.
11. Disclosure Required by Law
We may disclose Personal Information when required by law or when we believe in good faith that such action is necessary in
order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a court order or legal process served upon ​www.​foodytv.com​ or any
of its officers or principals. We further reserve the right to disclose such information when ​www.​foodytv.com​ reasonably
believes that it is needed to identify, contact, or bring legal action against a party who may be violating ​www.​foodytv.com​'s
Terms of Use or may be causing injury to or interference with ​www.​foodytv.com​’s​ rights or property, registered customers or
potential customers of ​www.​foodytv.com​, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
12. Your Comments
www.Foodytv.com​ ​welcomes feedback concerning its Privacy Policy. Please send your comments and questions to
info@foodytv.com​.
